Finding Aid for the Norris Hundley Papers LSC.0577
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: City of Los Angeles vs. City of San Fernando, et al, 1794-1975
  - Subseries 2A: Indexes, circa 1970
    - Trial index, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
      Contains list of witnesses, table of cross references, subject matter index, chronological summary, and reporter's index.
  - Subseries 2B: Indexed exhibits, 1800-1970
    Indexed plaintiff and defendant exhibits, arranged by the original exhibit number.
    Researchers should use the indexes in Subseries 2A to see a full list of exhibits used in the case.
    - LA 1-125, undated; (1 item). (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Copies of exhibits, including Spanish, Mexican, and Anglo-American documents.
    - Reporter's transcript (LA 126-134), 1966 March 16-22; (1 item). (Box 48, Folder 2)
      Reporter's transcript vol.43, 12296-12617. Includes testimony of John Caughey, witness for the Plaintiff, on pueblo water rights. Assorted filings and exhibits.
    - LA 126-155, undated; (1 item). (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Clerk's transcript (LA 154-214), 1966 March 21-23; (1 item). (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Clerk's transcript vol.15, 4058-4351. Copies of exhibits.
    - LA 156-216, undated; (1 item). (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Clerk's transcript (LA 215-281), 1966 March 23; (1 item). (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Clerk's transcript vol. 16, 4352-4653. Copies of exhibits.
    - LA 217-269, undated; (1 item). (Box 50, Folder 1)
      Copies of exhibits, including manuscripts and transcripts.
    - LA 270, 1863; (1 item). (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Colonial history of San Francisco, by John W. Dwinelle.
    - LA 271, undated; (1 item). (Box 50, Folder 3)
      The pueblo water right of Los Angeles, historically considered. Outline of testimony, divided into the chapters of Caughey's treatise.
    - LA 271a, 1959; (1 item). (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Revised treatise.
    - LA 272, undated; (1 item). (Box 50, Folder 5)
      John Caughey testimony: Conclusions re existence and water right of the pueblo of Los Angeles.
    - LA 273-280, undated; (5 items). (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Additional exhibit references with photographs and lists.
    - LA 281, 1906; (1 item). (Box 51, Folder 1)
      The City of Los Angeles vs. Hunter. Pleadings, findings and judgments regarding over Los Angeles River and water usage.
    - LA 282, 1904; (1 item). (Box 51, Folder 2)
      The City of Los Angeles vs. Thomas D. Buffington, et al. Transcripts of complaint, pleadings, findings, and judgments.
    - LA 283, 1936; (1 item). (Box 51, Folder 3)
      The City of Los Angeles vs. The City of Glendale. Transcripts of complaint, pleadings, findings, and judgments.
    - LA 284, 1933-1941; (1 item). (Box 51, Folder 4)
      City of Los Angeles vs. The City of Burbank. Complaints, answers, findings and judgments.
    - LA 285, undated; (1 item). (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Pleadings and judgments. Pomeroy & Hooker, West Los Angeles Water Company, Los Angeles Farming and Milling, Laguna Irrigation Company, and Amestoy Estate Company cases.
    - LA 290-291, undated; (3 items). (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Water rights of the pueblo of Los Angeles, by William B. Stern: study of property laws under Spanish and Mexican regional laws. Statement to the court.
    - LA 292, 1856-1882; (2 items). (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Patent to the City of Los Angeles Under the Federal Land Claims Act. Copies of declaration, stipulations, dismissal of appeal and patent records 1876, 1878, 1882.
    - LA 293, 1848 February 2; (1 item). (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Treaty of Guadalupe Hidalgo.
    - LA 294, 1851-1957; (3 items). (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Land Commission Act and California Land Commission decision no. 280 (oversize copy of original petition).
    - LA 295, 1906-1908; (1 item). (Box 52, Folder 5)
      City of Los Angeles vs. The Los Angeles Farming and Milling Company Filings re water use and water rights of the Los Angeles River.
    - LA 296-297, undated; (2 items). (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Photograph of L.A. and a photocopy.
    - LA 298-300, 1957 July; (3 items). (Box 52, Folder 7)
      Notice of pendancy of action.
      Amended and supplemental notice of pendancy of action.
      Photocopy re the Department of Water and Power.
    - LA 313-406c, 1966 September-April; (1 item). (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Clerk's transcript, Vol. 22, 6160-6380.
    - Def. 1 (folder 1 of 2), 1966 June 22; (1 item). (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Clerk's transcript vol. 26, 7274-7574. A study on laws and customs pertaining to the use of water in California under Spain and Mexico (Rolle and Wilson).
    - Def. 1 (folder 2 of 2), 1966 June 22; (1 item). (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Clerk's transcript vol. 27, 7575-7870. Defendant's Exhibit 1, continued.
    - Def. 2-10, circa 1959; (9 items). (Box 54, Folder 1)
      Assorted exhibits for the joint Defendants.
    - Def. 11-19, 1800-1969 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      Copies of manuscripts used as evidence in in Land Grant hearings.
    - Def. 20, 1852 October 7; (1 item). (Box 54, Folder 3)
      Southern District of California Eulogio de Celis, Appellee, vs. The United States, Appellant. Transcript.
    - Def. 21, 1852 September 11 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      David W. Alexander, et al. vs. The United States. Transcript of the proceedings for the place named "Providencia."
    - Def. 22, 1852 November 8; (1 item). (Box 54, Folder 5)
      David W. Alexander, et. al. vs. The United States. Transcript of the proceedings for the place named "Cahuenga."
    - Def. 23, 1852 September 11; (1 item). (Box 54, Folder 6)
      Maria Ygnacia Verdugo vs. The United States. Transcript of the proceedings for the place named "Los Feliz."
    - Def. 24, undated; (1 item). (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Titles: Rancho ex-mission de San Fernando, Rancho Providencia, Cahuenga, Rancho Los Felis, Rancho San Rafael, Rancho Tujunga, Rancho La Canada, Rancho Encino.
    - Def. 25-26, 1862-1875; (2 items). (Box 55, Folder 2)
      Copies of maps from recorded patents of land grants; Excerpts from "The colonial history of the city of San Francisco" by John Dwinelle (1866), dealing with legation between the city of San Francisco and the United States for that city's claim to four leagues of pueblo land.
    - Def. 27, 1849-1850; (1 item). (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Excerpts from the statutes of California, passed in the years 1850-1925.
    - Def. 28-36, 38-40, undated; 12 items). (Box 55, Folder 4)
      Copies of various exhibits.
    - Def. 41, undated; (1 item). (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Memorandum reviewing the basic legal principles relative to water rights in California under Spain and Mexico, by Laudelino Moreno.
    - Def. 42, 1966 October 27; (1 item). (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Discursive analysis of Onate's Memorandum on the right to use water under the laws of Spain and Mexico prior to February 2, 1848, by William B. Offner.
    - SF 1, undated; (1 item). (Box 55, Folder 7)
      Robert E. Moore, Deputy City Attorney, correspondence regarding Land Claims Commission.
    - GB 1-34, circa 1959; (9 items). (Box 55, Folder 8)
      Assorted exhibits. Includes chronological analysis of Los Angeles region and a copy of water grants in different jurisdictions taken from the General Archives of the Nation, Mexico City.
    - CV 1, 1852 October 21; (1 item). (Box 56, Folder 1)
      San Rafael patent. Transcripts of the proceedings in the case of Julio Berdugo vs. United States.
    - CV 2, 1852-1882; (1 item). (Box 56, Folder 2)
      Scott Hayes vs. The United States. La Canada transcript.
    - CV 3-6, 1882; (4 items). (Box 56, Folder 3)
      San Rafael patent map.
      Los Angeles patent map.
      T.I. Rancho map.
      Petition for appeal submitted by Jonathan R. Scott and Benjamin Hayes, 1852.
  - Subseries 2C: Miscellaneous exhibits, 1794-1958
    Unidentified and unmarked material, most likely used in the case.
    - Records of the General Land Office, 1874-1876; (1 item). (Box 56, Folder 4)
      A binder of over 50 copied documents from the National Archives re the pueblo of Los Angeles. Index in the front of binder.
    - Exhibits, circa 1794-1855; (4 items). (Box 57, Folder 1-4)
      - Incomplete binder of many exhibits, 1794-1855; (1 item). (Box 57, Folder 1)
        Presumably related to Los Angeles pueblo rights. Partial index.
      - Binder of exhibits, undated; (1 item). (Box 57, Folder 2)
        Laws of the kingdom of the Indies.
        History of the pueblo of Los Angeles.
        History of Glendale and vicinity.
        Burbank--The water problem; Treaty--United States and Mexico, 1853.
      - Spanish and English documents, undated; (1 item). (Box 57, Folder 3)
        re pueblos and property rights under Spain and Mexico. Includes Table of Contents.
      - Notes, undated; (1 item). (Box 57, Folder 4)
        Notes on summary of laws for the kingdom of the Indies; Notes on Escriche and ordinances of lands and waters.
    - City of Los Angeles map, 1849 August 29; (2 items). (Box 57, Folder 5)
      Plan de la Cuidad de Los Angeles.
    - Hart vs. Burnett, 1860; (1 item). (Box 57, Folder 6)
      Transcript of case regarding pueblo lands of the city of San Francisco.
    - Reglamento e instruccion para los presidios, undated; (1 item). (Box 57, Folder 7)
      Rules and instructions for presidios in New Spain. Typewritten transcription.
    - San Fernando water report, 1958 March; (1 item). (Box 58, Folder 1)
      Official report: City of San Fernando report on water supply and demand of pueblo of Los Angeles.
    - Spanish-English vocabulary, undated; (1 item). (Box 58, Folder 2)
      Spanish-English vocabulary guide designed for use in City of Los Angeles vs. City of San Fernando et al., with review by H.B. Crummett.
  - Subseries 2D: Filings, 1969-1975
    Assorted briefs and motions in single bound volumes.
    - Opening brief, 1969 June 17; (1 item). (Box 58, Folder 3)
      Opening brief of appellant the city of Los Angeles. Topical index and table of contents included.
    - Appendix to the opening brief, 1969 June (Box 58, Folder 4)
      Appendices A, B, and C.
    - Supplemental opening brief, 1970 November; (1 item). (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Topical index included.
    - Appendix to the supplemental opening brief, 1970 November; (1 item). (Box 58, Folder 6)
      List of appendices included.
    - Respondent's brief, 1971 September 6; (1 item). (Box 58, Folder 7)
      vol.2. Topical index included.
    - Appendix to the respondent's brief, 1971 August; (1 item). (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Appendices A-F.
    - Reply brief, 1972 April 28; (1 item). (Box 59, Folder 2)
      Reply brief of appellant the city of Los Angeles. Includes topical index.
    - Action, 1975 May 12; (1 item). (Box 59, Folder 3)
      Action filed by City of Los Angeles to obtain its prior rights to the Upper Los Angeles River Area.
- Series 3: The Great Thirst and other publications, circa 1808-2009
  Assorted research materials, including forty-six 3.5 inch floppy disks and five CDs related to Hundley's publications and research.
  Arranged in five subseries:
  3A. Clippings, 1973-1999
  3B. Microfilm, slides, negatives, and photographs, 1920-1966
  3C. Research files, ca. 1808-1999
  3D. Reviews, 1966-2002
  3E. Digital materials, 1994-2005
  See also Series 2 and Series 4.
  - Subseries 3A: Clippings, 1973-2007
    Assorted newspaper clippings re water usage.
    - Agriculture subsidies, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Big Green, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Bush and environment, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - California drought, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - California water (folder 1 of 2), 1973-1978 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - California water (folder 2 of 2), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - California water policy, 1982-1984 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Central Valley, 1987-1997 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Colorado River, 1989-1997 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Conservation, 1985-1992 (Box 90, Folder 10, Box 60)
    - Dams, 1993-1999 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Delta (CalFed), 1989-1999 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Democratic registration, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Desalination, 1990-1992 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Developers, 1993-1999 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Drought and aqueducts, 1987-1991 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Farmland and farmers, 1981-1998 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Flooding, 1995-1997 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Future water projects, 1985-1989 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Greenhouse effect, 1988-1990 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Heton Hetchy, 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Imperial Valley, 1988-1998 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Indian rights, 1982-1988 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Kesterson National Wildlife Refuge, 1989-1990 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Levees, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles Department of Water and Power, 1990-1999 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Los Angeles River, 1994-1999 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Medfly and Mexfly, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Metropolitan Water District (MWD), 1989-1999 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1999 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - MWD clipsheets, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Box 62, Box 63)
      - (folder 1 of 13), 1998 February (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - (folder 2 of 13), 1998 April (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - (folder 3 of 13), 1998 May (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - (folder 4 of 13), 1998 June (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - (folder 5 of 13), 1998 July (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - (folder 6 of 13), 1998 August (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - (7 of 13), 1998 September (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - (8 of 13), 1998 October-November (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - (9 of 13), 1998 December (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - (10 of 13), 1999 January (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - (11 of 13), 1999 February (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - (12 of 13), 1999 March (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - (13 of 13), 1999 April-June (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - MWD vs. San Diego, 1995-1999 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1999 (Box 63, Folder 3-7)
      - ., 1980-1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - ., 1982-1984 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - ., 1991 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - ., 1991-1993 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - ., 1991-1999 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Mono Lake, 1983-1999 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - New Melones Dam, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Owens Valley, 1981-1998 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Pesticides, 1988-1998 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Peripheral Canal, 1980-1982 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Planning, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Pollution, 1983-1999 (Box 64, Folder 7-11)
      - ., 1983-1998 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Beaches and coast, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Farmers, 1986-1990 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Groundwater, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Southern California, 1993-1999 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Population, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Power, 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Rainfall figures, 2005-2007 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Rice and birds, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Sacramento Bee, 1998-1999 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - San Fernando Valley, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco Bay, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Santa Barbara, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Southern California Edison, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - State vs. Federal, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Water subsidies, 1983-1996 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Wetlands, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Wild rivers, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Winters Doctrine, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 3B: Microfilm, slides, negatives, and photographs, 1920-1999
    The subseries contains microfilm, slides of vacation and family photographs, and lecture slides. Other materials include aerial photographs, and photographs of historical persons or sites used in the publication of Hundley's books and which are not originals.
    - Arizona vs. California et al, 1934; (1 item, microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 1)
      Library of Congress, 292 U.S. 341. Bills of complaint, filings, etc.
    - Arizona vs. California et al, 1936; (1 item, microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 2)
      Library of Congress, 298 U.S. 558. Bills of complaint, briefs, filings, etc.
    - Colorado River Project, 1934; (1 item, microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 3)
      National Archives, file 032, RG 48. Colorado River Compact and perpetuation of testimony re Arizona vs. California.
    - Department of Justice (DoJ) records, 1934; (1 item, microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 4)
      National Archives, file 234802-1, RG 60. DOJ correspondence file re Arizona vs. California.
    - League of the Southwest, 1920 April; (1 item, microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 5)
      Huntington Library. Proceedings of the third convention of the League at the Trinity Auditorium in Los Angeles, California.
    - Mexican Water Treaty, undated; (1 item, microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 6)
      UCLA. One volume entitled Mexican Water Treaty (appears to be a typescript/scrapbook).
    - Supreme Court and DoJ records, circa 1934; (1 item, positive microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 7)
      National Archives. Supreme Court of the United States, Appellate case file no.20464, RG 267 (transcript and correspondence). Department of Justice, file no.58730, RG 60.
    - Supreme Court and DoJ records, circa 1934; (1 item, negative microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - United States vs. Arizona, 1935; (1 item, microfilm). (Box 65, Folder 9)
      Library of Congress, 295 U.S. 174. Bills of complaint, filings, etc.
    - Mexican-American farm workers, 1966; (21 items, slides). (Box 65, Folder 10)
      Living conditions of farm workers in Delano, California.
    - Negatives, undated; (9 items). (Box 65, Folder 11)
      9 negatives of maps and views of California.
    - Slides of vacation and family photographs, 1952-1979; 1967-1968 (Box 88, Folder 5-12)
      Organization and Arrangement
      Each folder includes slides from the same carousel slide tray and the slide labels as captioned by Hundley. The slides are labelled with the corresponding number on the label sheet.
    - Lecture slides, 1966; 1969 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      The slides include photographs of historical buildings, locations, groups, and persons in California and/or the American Southwest. Some of the slides are labelled.
    - Montgomery March slides, 1965 March (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Water and the West photographs and maps, 1975 June 30 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - The Great Thirst photographs, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 4-5)
  - Subseries 3C: Research files, circa 1808-2009
    Assorted research materials and maps, arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - Abbott, Warren, 1986, 1997; (2 items). (Box 66, Folder 1)
      Publications: Myth vs. Reality: Agricultural Subsidies and the State Water Project; Water Conflict in the Western United States.
    - Anastacio Feliz, et al. vs. City of Los Angeles, circa 1881; (3 items). (Box 66, Folder 2)
      Complaints, briefs, and points and authorities regarding Lois Ranchos Feliz and its ownership, usage, and rights (including water from the Los Angeles River).
    - Bancroft, Hubert Howe, undated; (2 items). (Box 66, Folder 3)
      Typewritten notes on his History of the Pacific States of North America.
    - Beck, Robert (Ed.), 1998-1999; (7 items). (Box 66, Folder 4)
      Waters and water rights.
    - Bradley, Karen J., 1993 August; (1 item). (Box 66, Folder 5)
      Essay: Who would benefit? Debating the distribution of the Central Valley Project's subsidies.
    - California: A History of a Remarkable State revision and updates, 1983, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - California congressional votes, 1959-1989; (10 items). (Box 66, Folder 6)
      Contains copies of California Senatorial Districts/Areas and vote breakdown.
    - California Journal, 1995-1996; (10 items). (Box 66, Folder 7)
      Assorted issues.
    - California State Coastal Conservancy, 1984 July 20; (1 item). (Box 66, Folder 8)
      Memorandum of Understanding Regarding the California State Coastal Conservancy San Francisco Bay Wetland Mitigation Bank Program, North Bank Site.
    - Central Valley Project Improvement Act, undated; (7 items). (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - City of Los Angeles; DWP vs. Board of Supervisors of the County of Inyo, 1991; (1 item). (Box 66, Folder 10)
      Stipulation and Order for Judgment.
    - City of Los Angeles vs. Leon Mc L. Baldwin et al, 1877-1878; (4 items). (Box 66, Folder 11)
      Transcript on appeal, points and authorities, and findings and facts related to Los Angeles river water rights and privileges.
    - Coachella Valley Water District, 1996, 1999; (4 items). (Box 67, Folder 1)
      Contains:
      General Manager's Open Letter (1996).
      Key Terms for Quantification Settlement Among the State of California, IID, CVWD, and MWD (1999).
      Synopsis of Quantification Settlement Among IID, CVWD and MWD (1999).
      Agreement for the implementation of a test land fallowing program and use of saved water.
    - Coalition for a Fair Water Policy, 1995-1996; (15 items). (Box 67, Folder 2)
      Printed material regarding the Imperial Valley and San Diego water deals.
    - Coate, Charles, 1995 August 5; (1 item). (Box 67, Folder 3)
      Paper: "Critical Turning Points in Federal Reclamation Policy."
    - Colorado River Commission, 1927; (2 items). (Box 67, Folder 4)
      Photograph and negative of Colorado River Commission members at the Grand Canyon (from the Nevada Historical Society).
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999; (ca. 20 items). (Box 67, Folder 5)
      Correspondence regarding various California water areas and projects, including the Imperial Valley, San Diego, Coachella, Santa Monica, and the Central Valley.
    - County of Inyo vs. City of Los Angeles and DWP, 1997; (7 items). (Box 67, Folder 6)
      Filings.
    - Davis, Author Powell, 1915-1934; (18 items). (Box 67, Folder 8)
      Copies of letters and documents from the Author Powell Davis papers at the University of Wyoming (Davis was the consulting engineer for the Boulder Dam).
    - Crandell, John, 1994; (1 item). (Box 67, Folder 7)
      Essay: "Los Angeles: A Century of Agriculture in the Valley of the Pueblo."
    - DBCP, 1989; (1 item). (Box 67, Folder 9)
      Article: DBCP in drinking water: what does it mean?
    - The Great Thirst revisions, graphs, maps, and figures, 1994-1999 (Box 89, Folder 7-11)
    - Hall, William H., 1886, 1888; (2 items, photocopies). (Box 67, Folder 10)
      Excerpts: Irrigation development (1886) and Irrigation in California (1888).
    - Heavy Ground revisions, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Henry Elms et al. vs. City of Los Angeles, 1881; (2 items). (Box 67, Folder 11)
      Petitions and points and authorities regarding Henry Elms' rehearing on case regarding water usage and rights.
    - Los Angeles City Archives, 1850 July 8; (1 item). (Box 67, Folder 12)
      Translations from the Spanish re report from the special committee on water supply.
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs highway maps, 1978-1988 (Oversize-box 93, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      This box contains Bureau of Indian Affairs highway maps for the Papago Indian Agency and Pascua Yaqui Reservation, Pima County, and Fort Yumi Indian Agency maps for the West and East Cocopah Reservation in Arizona.
    - California maps, undated (Oversize-box 93, Folder 2)
      This box contains 26 maps of Californian water districts, rainfall, waterways, canals and state projects. All of the maps were used in The Great Thirst.
    - Martinez Report., undated; (2 items). (Box 68, Folder 1)
      Assorted typewritten notes on water cases and Spanish documents.
    - Metropolitan Water District (MWD) of Southern California, 1988-1999; (19 items). (Box 68, Folder 2)
      Newsletters, marketing materials, official statistics, maps, and the 1996-1997 annual financial report.
    - MWD of Southern California vs. All Persons...., 1998; (5 items). (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - MWD of Southern California: Oshio letters, 1993-1997 (Box 89, Folder 13)